Finding Aid for BMC Media Services records, 1851-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - P-R
    - Pop-Busui, Rodica, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Potchynok, Mary, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Powers, Holly, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Poznanski, Andrew, 1968; 1976 (Box 7)
    - Poznanski, Elva, Psychiatry, 1973; 1976 (Box 7)
    - Prager, Richard, Cardiac Surgery, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Prescott, Albert B., undated (Box 7)
    - Preuss, Leslie, Psychology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Prielipp, Amy, Nursing, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Pritts, Jill, Reproductive Sciences, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Przybyla, Rachel, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Punch, Jeffrey, Surgery, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Punch, Margaret, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Punnett, Angela, Pediatrics, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Quan, Taihao, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Quinn, James, Emergency Medicine, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Quint, Elizabeth, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Rachwal, William, Surgery, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Racine, Michael, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Rae, James W. (includes wife), Physical Medicine, 1961; 1971; undated (Box 7)
    - Raghunathan, Trivellore Eachambadi, School of Public Health (Box 7)
    - Ramnath, Suresh, Neurosurgery, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Ramsey, Jill, Sports Medicine, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Randolph, John F., Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Ransom, Henry K., Surgery, 1959; undated (Box 7)
    - Rapp, Robert, Radiology, undated (Box 7)
    - Rasmussen, James, Pediatric Dermatology, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Ratanatharathorn, Voravit, Internal Medicine, Hematology and Oncology, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Ratliff, Rigdon K., 1968 (Box 7)
    - Raver, Marci, Cardiovascular Center, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Reame, Nancy, Nursing, 1997; 2001 (Box 7)
    - Reed, (?), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Regan, William J., 1968; undated (Box 7)
    - Rehman, Khurram, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Reichert, Rudolph E. Jr, 1950 (Box 7)
    - Reinish, Ed, Oral Surgery, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Remaley, Jodette, Neurology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Ren, Xiadon, Neurosurgery, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Reuter, (?), undated (Box 7)
    - Rexer, Mary, Cancer Center, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Reynolds, (?), Heart Station, 1967; 1968; 1971 (Box 7)
    - Reynolds, Christopher, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Reynolds, Kevin, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999; undated (Box 7)
    - Rhee, Shang- Youl, Physical Medicine, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Riba, Michelle, Psychiatry, 1996; 1998 (Box 7)
    - Richards, Bob, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Richards, Jennifer, Orthotics and Prosthetics, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Riegger, Lori, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Rigg, (?), undated (Box 7)
    - Riggs, Thomas, 1981 (Box 7)
    - Riley, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Ringler, Dan, Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Riskalla, Mona, Pediatrics, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Ritter, Frank N., 1963 (Box 7)
    - Roberts, Catherine, Otolaryngology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Roberts, James, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Robertson, Erle, Microbiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Robertson, Patricia, Neurology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Robillard, Jean, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Robinson, Carl, Neurology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Robinson, J.O., 1956 (Box 7)
    - Robinson, William D., Internal Medicine, 1958; 1968; undated (Box 7)
    - Rocchini, Albert, Pediatrics 1998, 2001 (see also Shaltis, Barbara, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998) (Box 7)
    - Rodin, Ernst A., 1956 (Box 7)
    - Rodziewicz, Catherine, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Rodziewicz, Thomas, Anesthesiology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Roessler, Blake, Rheumatology, undated (Box 7)
    - Roller, Sony, Nursing, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Ronis, David, Nursing, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Rose, Homer, Rackham Graduate School, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Rosen, David, Internal Medicine, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Rosenberg, Andrew, Anesthesiology, Internal Medicine, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Rosenberg, Jack, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Rosenthal, Amnon, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Ross, Alan, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Rottman, Keith, Oral Surgery, undated (Box 7)
    - Rouff, Lisa, Psychology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Rovner, David R. (?), undated (Box 7)
    - Royce, Toni, Claims Office, 1956; 1970; 1975 (Box 7)
    - Rubenfire, Melvyn, Cardiology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Ruddon, Raymond, Pharmacology, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Rushton, Jerry, General Pediatrics and Health Services Research, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Russell, James, Neurology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Russell, Rhoda, Reddig, School of Nursing Dean, 1962; 1999 (Box 7)
    - Ruthven, Alexander, undated (Box 7)
    - Rutledge, Lester T. (?), Physiology, undated (Box 7)
  - S-T
    - Sager, Abram, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Saint, David, Thoracic Surgery, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Sakada, Harry S., 1955 (Box 7)
    - Sakurai, Sharin, Neurology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Samyn, Margaret, Pediatric Cardiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sanborn, John, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Sanchez, Gisela, Anesthesiology 1997 see Pierce, Kathy, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Sanchez, Lucy, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Sandeep, Vijan, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Sanford, Theodore J., Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Santinga, John T., Heart Station, 1970; 1973; 1989; 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sarbach, Douglas L., 1977 (Box 7)
    - Sarosi, George, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sasson, Lior, Pediatric Cardiology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Sataloff, Robert, Otolaryngology, undated (Box 7)
    - Savageau, Michael, Microbiology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Saxe, Stephen, Ophthalmology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Scelza, William, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Schaberg, Dennis, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Schact, Jochen, Biological Chemistry, Otolaryngology, 1997; 1999; 2000 (Box 7)
    - Schafer, Jennifer, Family Practice, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Schallert, Timothy "Tim", Psychology, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Scharenberg, Konstantin(?), undated (Box 7)
    - Scheiman, Lisa, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Schielke, Gerald, Neurosurgery, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Schimpf, Megan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Schmaier, Alec, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Schmickel, Roy, Pediatrics, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Schmickle, (?), 1973 (Box 7)
    - Schneider, Jan, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Schneider, Richard C., Neurosurgery, 1953; 1962; 1973; 1983; 1984 (Box 7)
    - undated (Box 7)
    - Schteingart, David E., 1962; 1996; undated (Box 7)
    - Schultz, Carol, Surgery, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Schumacher, Robert, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Schwartz, Alan, undated (Box 7)
    - Schwartz, Ed, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Schweiger, Winifred, Anesthesiology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Schwenk, Thomas, Family Practice, 1989; 1992 (Box 7)
    - Scott, Bennie B., Neurosurgery, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Scott, Phillip, Emergency Services, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Seeger, Joachim F., Radiology, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Seevers, Maurice H., Pharmacology, 1951; 1969; 1970; undated (Box 7)
    - Seiler, Andrew, Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Selden, Nathan, Neurosurgery, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Selim, Alexandra, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Selman, David G., undated (Box 7)
    - Serlin, David, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Serwer, Gerald, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Severin, John, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Shadigian, Elizabeth, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994; 1996 (Box 7)
    - Shaltis, Barbara, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Shane, (?), Sports Medicine, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Shanmugham, Kalpana, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Sharma, Manish, Nuclear Medicine, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Shaw, Catherine, School of Public Policy, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Shayman, James, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001; undated (Box 7)
    - Shea, Michael J., Internal Medicine, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Sheagren, John, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Sheets, Kent, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Sheetz, Mrs. (J. Kathryn?), undated (Box 7)
    - Shehab, Thomas, Internal Medicine, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Sheinberg, Michael, Neurology, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sheldon, "Pop", undated (Box 7)
    - Sheldon, John M. (includes wife), 1946; 1959; undated (Box 7)
    - Shen, Tim, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Shepherd, (?)Gerontology, undated (Box 7)
    - Sherman, Ed L., 1976 (Box 7)
    - Sherrod, (?), Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Shiba, Kaduhiro, Nuclear Medicine, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Shier, Janice, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Shin, K., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Shin, Patrick, Surgery, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Shlafer, Marshal, Pharmacology, undated (Box 7)
    - Shoemaker, John C., 1955 (Box 7)
    - Shukait, Michelle, Medical Administration, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Shultheis, Carol, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 7)
    - Sierra, Jane, Medical School Administration, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Silbergleit, Robert, Emergency Medicine, 1997; undated (Box 7)
    - Silva, Joseph, Jr., Internal Medicine, 1975; 1977 (Box 7)
    - Silver, Samuel, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Silver, Terry, Radiology, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Silverman, (?), 1971; undated (Box 7)
    - Sing, (?), undated (Box 7)
    - Sippola- Thiele, Maria, Technology Transfer Office, 1999 (Box 7)
    - Sission, James C., 1961 (Box 7)
    - Skaddan, Marc, Nuclear Medicine, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Skinner, Geraldine, School of Nursing, undated (Box 7)
    - Sletten, Karin, Ophthalmology, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Sloan, Herbert E., Thoracic Surgery 19611963, 1959; 1967; 1972 (Box 7)
    - Smith, (?), 1949 (Box 7)
    - Smith, (?), Allergy, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Smith, David J., Plastic Surgery, 1993 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Donald C., 1968 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Ed, Physical Medicine, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Gary G., Gift of Art Program, undated (Box 7)
    - Smith, Gary D., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999; 2000 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Howard, Surgery, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Jeffrey, Primary Care, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Stewart, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Smith, William M., undated (Box 7)
    - Smith, Yolanda, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 7)
    - Smith, Yolanda, Pharmacology, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Smolens, Iva, Thoracic Surgery, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Smoyer, William, Pediatrics and Communicable Diseases, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Sniderman, Stephen P., 1963 (Box 8)
    - Snow, Joseph, Psychology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Soldes, Oliver, General Surgery, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Solomon, William, 1967; undated (Box 8)
    - Song, Julie, Radiology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Sonis, Jeffrey, Family Medicine, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Southwell, D., Credit Union, undated (Box 8)
    - Sowers, Mary Fran, Epidemiology, Obstetrics and Gynecology School of Public Health, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Spahlinger, David, Primary Care, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Sparks, H., undated (Box 8)
    - Sparks, Wendy, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Spearman, Dara, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Speights, Steven, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Spicer, Deidre, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Spires, M. Catherine, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Stalburg, Caren, undated (Box 8)
    - Standiford, Theodore, Pulmonology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Stanger, Nicole, Neurology, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Stanley, James C., Surgery, 1973; 1980 (Box 8)
    - Stanton, Michael, Neurology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Stanwood, Nancy, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 8)
    - Stark, Paul S., Administration, 1977 (Box 8)
    - Starling, Mark, Cardiology, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Stawiski, Marek A., Dermatology, 1974; 1976 (Box 8)
    - Stefanelli, Tammi, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Steinberg, Brett, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Steinstraesser, Lars, Surgery, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Stephens, David C., 1973 (Box 8)
    - Stern, Aaron M., 1959; undated (Box 8)
    - Steude, Georgine, Anesthesiology, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Stevens, Christine, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Stevens, Martin, Endocrinology and Metabolism, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Stevenson, Harold W., Center for Human Growth and Development, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Stevenson, Thomas Ray, Plastic Surgery, 1985; 1989 (Box 8)
    - Stevenson, Ann L., Pathology, undated (Box 8)
    - Stewart, Kellie, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Steyer, Terrence, Internal Medicine, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Stickney, Sandra, Nursing, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Stoll, Stefan, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Stoolman, Lloyd, Pathology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Story, Kristen, HRD, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Stout, (?), Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Stoyanoff, Peter, Emergency Medicine, undated (Box 8)
    - Stribley, John, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Strickberger, Adam, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Strieter, Robert, Pulmonary, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Stross, Jeoffrey, Internal Medicine, 1990; 1992; undated (Box 8)
    - Stryker, Nancy, Nursing, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Stump, Lawrence, Anesthesiology, 1997; 2001 (Box 8)
    - Sturgis, Cyrus C., Internal Medicine, 1940s; undated (Box 8)
    - Sturza, Henry, Appliance Shop, 1968 (Box 8)
    - Su, Grace, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Sugaward, (?), Nuclear Medicine, undated (Box 8)
    - Sullivan, Donita, 1962 (Box 8)
    - Sullivan, Shannon, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Sung, Randall, Surgery, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Suzuki, Masahiko, Nuclear Medicine, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Suzuki, Yoshi, Pediatric Cardiology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Swain, Henry H., 1957; 1989 (Box 8)
    - Swartz, Richard, Nephrology, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Sweet, Jeffrey, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Sweet, Robert B., Anesthesiology, 1960 (Box 8)
    - Swett, Jay, General Surgery, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Taihao, Quan, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Tang, Hsin-Yi, Pharmacology, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Tannen, Richard, Internal Medicine, 1986; 1988 (Box 8)
    - Taren, James A., Neurosurgery, 1955; 1958; 1962; 1964; 1967; 1968; 1977; 1978; undated (Box 8)
    - Tarolli, Janet, Research Associate at Cancer Center, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Tate, Denise, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Taylor, Dale L., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Taylor, Jack N. (?), Urology, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Taylor, Kathleen, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Taylor, Robert, 1949 (Box 8)
    - Taylor, William B., Dermatology, 1953; undated (Box 8)
    - Tew, Jessica, Reproductive Science Program, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Thaxton, Melissa, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Thoen, Jess, Pediatrics (includes wife), 1983; 1995 (Box 8)
    - Thomas, Hugh Owen (copy) (includes Robert Jones), 1885 (Box 8)
    - Thomas, Lamar, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Thompson, (?), Surgery, undated (Box 8)
    - Thompson, B. Gregory, Neurosurgery, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Thompson, Nancy, Biophysics, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Thornbury, John R., undated (Box 8)
    - Thornton, James W., Surgery, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Thorson, Jayne, Dean of Faculty Affairs, 1997; 2001 (Box 8)
    - Threatt, Barbara A., Radiology, 1978 (Box 8)
    - Todd, Robert, Internal Medicine, 1995; 1999; 2000; 2001 (Box 8)
    - Toews, Galen, Internal Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Tolbert, Rhonda, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Tolooi, Hadi, Neurology, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Tomford, Donald, Neurosurgery, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Tong, Hank, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Topol, Eric, Cardiology, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Torence, (?), Pediatric Oncology, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Torizuka, Tatsuo, Nuclear Medicine, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Tourtellotte, Wallace, Neurology, 1957; 1958; 1965; 1967; undated (Box 8)
    - Townly, Mary Lou, undated (Box 8)
    - Towsley, Harry A. (includes wife), Pediatrics, 1964; 1965; 1970; 1973; undated (Box 8)
    - Treloar, David, Pediatrics, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Tremper, Amy, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 8)
    - Tremper, Kevin, Anesthesiology, 2000; undated (Box 8)
    - Troen, Bruce, Geriatrics, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Trudeau, Michelle, Human Genetics, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Tsou, Carol, Family Practice, undated (Box 8)
    - Tubergen, David G., Pediatrics, undated (Box 8)
    - Tuck, Hope, 1948 (Box 8)
    - Tupper, (?), 1960 (Box 8)
    - Turcotte, Jeremiah, Surgery, 1972; 1973; 1978 (Box 8)
    - Turgeon, Kim, Internal Medicine, 1991 (Box 8)
  - U-Z
    - Uberti, Joseph, Internal Medicine, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Uffner, Susan, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Upchurch, Gilbert, Vascular Surgery, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Upton, L. George, Oral Surgery, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Urbanchek, Melanie, Plastic Surgery, 1996 (Box 8)
    - Ushiro, Ernie, 1961 (Box 8)
    - Valentin, Cliff, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Valli, Denise, Internal Medicine, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Van Alstine, Fred, Family Practice, 1979 (Box 8)
    - Van De Ven, Cosmas, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Van Ittersum, Koryn, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Van Mater, David, Human Genetics, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Van Zwaluwenburg, James G., Radiology, undated (Box 8)
    - Vander Borght, Thierry, Nuclear Medicine, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Vander Hyde, Kristi, Infection Control & Epidemiology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vander, Arthur, Physiology, 1981; 1989 (Box 8)
    - Vanderkerkhove, Kristine, Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 8)
    - Vandermade, Minor, 1956; 1968 (Box 8)
    - VanderSteen, (?), Laboratory Animal Medicine, 1970 (Box 8)
    - Vanselow, Neal A., 1973; undated (Box 8)
    - Vassoff, Gus, 1959 (Box 8)
    - Vaughn, Victor, undated (Box 8)
    - Ver Meulen, Victor (Box 8)
    - Villa, Karen, Psychology, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vincent-Mark, Arlene, Population Fellow, School of Public Health, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Vlachos, Katrina, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Vlessis, Angelo, Thoracic Surgery, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Von Lubitz, Dag, Emergency Medicine, 1997; undated (Box 8)
    - Voorhees, John J., Dermatology, 1969; 1973; 1974; 1976; 1977; 1980; 1981; 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 8)
    - Votaw, Charles Lesley, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Waggoner, Raymond W. (includes family), Psychiatry, 1956; 1962; 1966; 1968; undated (Box 8)
    - Wahl, Richard, Nuclear Medicine, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Wakefield, Fran, Anesthesiology, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Wakefield, Thomas, Vascular Surgery, 1996; undated (Box 8)
    - Walker, Deborah, Nursing, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Walker, Sarah, Medical School Administration, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Wallace, John, 1963; undated (Box 8)
    - Wallner, Julius M., Psychiatry, 1953; 1959; undated (Box 8)
    - Walsh, (?), Cardiology, undated (Box 8)
    - Wampler, Stephen, Family Medicine, undated (Box 8)
    - Wang, Hui Qin, Dermatology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Wang, Lee, Psychiatry, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Wang, Qing, Anesthesiology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Wang, Xi, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Wang, Zhiqui, Neurosurgery, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Wannee, (?), Surgery, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Wanty, Suzanne, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994; undated (Box 8)
    - Ward, Michael, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Ward, Peter, Pathology, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Warfield, Louis M., Internal Medicine, undated (Box 8)
    - Warner, Pat, Ambulatory Care, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Warren, Lary, Medical Administration 1996, 1998, 1999 (includes picture of Warren with Gilbert Omenn) (Box 8)
    - Warthin, Aldred Scott, undated (Box 8)
    - Washburn, Jason, Psychiatry, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Washington, Julie, 1997; undated (Box 8)
    - Wasserman, (?), 1949 (Box 8)
    - Watkins, Paul, Internal Medicine, 1994; undated (Box 8)
    - Watson, Andrew S., Law and Psychiatry, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Watts, Charles, Clinical Affairs, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Webb, Bill, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Webb, R. Clinton, Physiology, undated (Box 8)
    - Wechsler, Stephanie, Pediatric Cardiology, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Weder, Alan, Internal Medicine, 2000; 2001 (Box 8)
    - Weg, John G., Internal Medicine, Pulmonary Disease, 1979 (Box 8)
    - Wegner, Jill, Bone Marrow Transplant, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Weick, Jacqueline, Bone Marrow Transplant 1999 also see Parker, Peggy, Bone Marrow Transplant Program, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Weigl, (?), 1998 (Box 8)
    - Wein, Theodore, Neurology, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Weinberg, (?), undated (Box 8)
    - Weinberg, Naimah Z., Psychiatry, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Weinstein, Jamie, Family Medicine, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Wesiman, Carol, Health Management and Policy, School of Public Health, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Weiss, Stephen, Internal Medicine and Oncology, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Weissman, (?), Nuclear Medicine, 1993 (Box 8)
    - Weller, Carl Vernon (includes wife), Internal Medicine, 1966; 1970; undated (Box 8)
    - Wening, Jason, Biomedical Engineering, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Wentz, Susan, Family Practice, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Werns, Steven, Cardiology, undated (Box 8)
    - Wesley, John, Pediatric Surgery, undated (Box 8)
    - West, Christine, Reproductive Sciences, 1997 (Box 8)
    - Westerberg, Martha R., Neurology, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Westfall, John, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Westfall, Margaret, Cardiac Surgery, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Whall, Ann, Nursing, 1996; 2001 (Box 8)
    - Wheeler, Albert H., Dermatology, 1952; undated (Box 8)
    - White, Casey, Learning Resource Center, 1999 (Box 8)
    - White, David L. (?), Administration, 1977 (Box 8)
    - White, Dawn, 2001 (Box 8)
    - White, Stew, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Whitecloud, Jacques, Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 8)
    - Whitehouse, Walter M., Radiology, 1965; 1967; 1969; undated (Box 8)
    - Wicha, Max S., Internal Medicine, 1983; 1988 (Box 9)
    - Widmayer, Clyde, Dietetics, undated (Box 9)
    - Wiggins, Roger, Internal Medicine, Nephrology, 1994; 1997; 2000; 2001 (Box 9)
    - Wilcox, Steve, Sports Medicine, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Wile, Udo (includes family), undated (Box 9)
      (see also outsize print in drawer 230)
    - Wiley, John, Internal Medicine, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Wiley, Richard A., Collection Manager, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Wilhelm, Kenneth "Ken", Endocrinology and Metabolism, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Wilkerson, William M., Surgery, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Williams, (?), 1989 (Box 9)
    - Williams, (?), Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Williams, Brent, Internal Medicine, 1996; 2000 (Box 9)
    - Williams, David M., Radiology, 1999 (Box 9)
    - Williams, J. W., 1927 (Box 9)
    - Williams, John, Physiology, 1996; 1999 (Box 9)
    - Williams, Reg, School of Nursing and Psychiatry, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Williams, Stuart W., Administration, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Willis, Park, III., Internal Medicine,1958, 1963; undated (Box 9)
    - Willson, Robert, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1952; undated (Box 9)
    - Wilson, Frank N. (includes wife), undated (Box 9)
    - Wilson, James, Internal Medicine, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Wilson, James L., undated (Box 9)
    - Winston, Harry, Anesthesiology, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Wintermeyer, Sue, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Wojtys, Edward, Sports Medicine, 1997 (Box 9)
    - Wolf, J. Stuart, Urology, 2000 (Box 9)
    - Wolfman, Earl F., 1960 (Box 9)
    - Wolson, Alan H., Radiology, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Wood, George (see Haynes, Harley) (Box 9)
    - Woodburne, Russell T., Anatomy, 1970; undated (Box 9)
    - Woods, John D., Nephrology, 1996 (Box 9)
    - Wooliscroft, James, Medical Education, 1987; 1999 (Box 9)
    - Worden, Frank, Internal Medicine, Hematology, Oncology, 2001 (Box 9)
    - Work, Bruce, Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1966; 1967; 1972; undated (Box 9)
    - Work, Walter P., 1977 (Box 9)
    - Wright, C., Obstetrics and Gynecology, undated (Box 9)
    - Wu, David, Ophthalmology, 2000 (Box 9)